buzka.com 2007-12-17

# Buzka • Privacy Policy

## Important information regarding your privacy

Buzka respects the privacy of all website users and is committed to protecting it. Information collected by Buzka will continue to be subject to this Privacy Policy.

### How we collect and use your information

Buzka may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use our Website and Services, post a link to the Buzka Website or submit questions, comments or bug reports.

In order to offer and provide optimum and personalised services, Buzka uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about our website users.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a Website User's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

Buzka never stores user information in any cookies that we use.

Buzka's Services give the Website User the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from Buzka.

Buzka may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our Website and Services.

Buzka may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our Website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Use.

Buzka may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type.

Buzka will never automatically send our users information/offers that our users do not want. Our users must choose to receive them.

Protecting the privacy of every user is important to Buzka and for that reason, Buzka will not collect age information of users under 18 years.

Buzka will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorisation from the appropriate user/s to do so otherwise.

### How we disclose your information

Unless required by law, Buzka will not share our users' personal information, IP addresses and usage information, except with your consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

### Changing your personal information

You can change your Buzka account information, profile and other information at any time.

Your Buzka account is password protected.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Buzka reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice.

If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will notify you of significant changes by posting a notice on our website so that you are aware of what information Buzka collects, how Buzka uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, Buzka discloses it.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website or your dealings with Buzka or would like further details about your records, you can send an email, in English, to [privacy@buzka.com](mailto:privacy@buzka.com).
